<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="56B8142A-05EA-43B5-9F21-9D5AE7CE12ED">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20151204" date="2015-12-04 21:48:21 +0000"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Ponderings&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Facepalm</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>    Have you ever been out in public and, as you&#x2019;re going on your way, you see someone from behind and are &lt;i&gt;absolutely&lt;/i&gt; sure it&#x2019;s a good friend of yours? So, like any good friend, you do something stupid and silly to mess with them--maybe you kick the back of their foot or say something really loud in their direction like &#x201C;RUN!!&#x201D; or &#x201C;OH MY GOODNESS!!&#x201D; I hope you do, because if not I feel like even &lt;i&gt;more&lt;/i&gt; of an idiot for doing what I did today.&#xD;    I was driving to my favorite coffeeshop, Bittersweet, to work on some homework. I was coming from my school and was in a procession of cars driven by other people who go to my school. There was a blue Mustang in front of me being driven by one of my fellow football players; he was a hilarious kid, always making jokes and acting crazy to get a laugh. In fact, every time we pass each other in the hallway we say, very seriously, &#x201C;Good job,&#x201D; and nod with mock severity. That always makes me smile. He also does a fantastic George Bush impression, and before football games he would BLAST hard rock and roll on our stereo while jumping up and down, bellowing, and contorting his face with intense righteous anger. &#xD;    I &lt;i&gt;knew&lt;/i&gt; it was him in the car. Same head, same hair, and... well, he drives a Mustang, right? I think I&#x2019;ve seen him get into it before. Yeah, I&#x2019;m certain it&#x2019;s him. &#xD;    We pull up to a stoplight, him right in front of me. Like any good friend, I start messing with him. &#xD;    My lights were off, so I switch them to park, then full, then park, then off, then park, then full, then park, then off, and so  on and so forth, then pause... all the while staring at him in his rear-view mirror. He looks confused, so I keep going, insanely frenetic with my three light settings. &lt;i&gt;This is great!&lt;/i&gt; I thought as he started looking around, and I went to full-blast craziness with my brights. &#xD;    Immediately my friend wheels around and stares right at me and... &#xD;    It&#x2019;s not him... &#xD;    &#xD;&#xD;&#xD;I stopped my flickering my lights at once, color rising fast and hot to my cheeks. My scalp started tingling as I looked off into the distance, trying to play it off. Oh, it was terrible; I felt so ashamed, so stupid, so ignorant and immature. I looked back into his rear-view mirror and saw that the stranger was &lt;i&gt;smoldering &lt;/i&gt;with anger and disdain. He was probably cursing me out; I saw his mouth angrily spit several words that I was content not to hear.&#xD;    This red light was eternal. I sat under his bewildered and furious stare for what felt like three millennia, trying as hard as I could to keep from meeting his stare and all the while making it worse by ignoring him. Finally, green triumphed over red and we awkwardly lurched forward. He raced off ahead of me and I breathed for the first time in years. &#xD;    I&#x2019;m such an idiot. Man... I felt, and still feel, beyond stupid and inconsiderate. How could I have mistaken him? How could I have messed like that with a complete stranger? He must hate me... and, honestly, at the moment I hoped he wouldn&#x2019;t call the police on this crazy-haired short kid in a little red pick-up truck. &#xD;    Truth is, he&#x2019;ll forget me in a matter of days. I&#x2019;ll forget too, but I make this record as something to laugh about in the future. *Sigh* Why do we do things like this?</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, December 4, 2015&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
