<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ponderings</title>
    <link>file://localhost/Users/joshuaeastman/Desktop/online/Online/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>A rambling seeker of righteousness, &lt;br/&gt;Reflecting and introspecting, &lt;br/&gt;Seeking truth in all things, &lt;br/&gt;Unveiling what is hidden, &lt;br/&gt;Sharing what is good, &lt;br/&gt;Pouring out love and longing, &lt;br/&gt;Glorifying God with every word and sentiment. </description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Facepalm</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/joshuaeastman/Desktop/online/Online/Blog/Entries/2015/12/4_Facepalm.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d734bbcc-6c04-4a38-b81d-2bd06f1122cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 4 Dec 2015 16:05:46 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>Have you ever been out in public and, as you’re going on your way, you see someone from behind and are absolutely sure it’s a good friend of yours? So, like any good friend, you do something stupid and silly to mess with them--maybe you kick the back of their foot or say something really loud in their direction like “RUN!!” or “OH MY GOODNESS!!” I hope you do, because if not I feel like even more of an idiot for doing what I did today.&lt;br/&gt;    I was driving to my favorite coffeeshop, Bittersweet, to work on some homework. I was coming from my school and was in a procession of cars driven by other people who go to my school. There was a blue Mustang in front of me being driven by one of my fellow football players; he was a hilarious kid, always making jokes and acting crazy to get a laugh. In fact, every time we pass each other in the hallway we say, very seriously, “Good job,” and nod with mock severity. That always makes me smile. He also does a fantastic George Bush impression, and before football games he would BLAST hard rock and roll on our stereo while jumping up and down, bellowing, and contorting his face with intense righteous anger. &lt;br/&gt;    I knew it was him in the car. Same head, same hair, and... well, he drives a Mustang, right? I think I’ve seen him get into it before. Yeah, I’m certain it’s him. &lt;br/&gt;    We pull up to a stoplight, him right in front of me. Like any good friend, I start messing with him. &lt;br/&gt;    My lights were off, so I switch them to park, then full, then park, then off, then park, then full, then park, then off, and so  on and so forth, then pause... all the while staring at him in his rear-view mirror. He looks confused, so I keep going, insanely frenetic with my three light settings. This is great! I thought as he started looking around, and I went to full-blast craziness with my brights. &lt;br/&gt;    Immediately my friend wheels around and stares right at me and... &lt;br/&gt;    It’s not him... &lt;br/&gt;    &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I stopped my flickering my lights at once, color rising fast and hot to my cheeks. My scalp started tingling as I looked off into the distance, trying to play it off. Oh, it was terrible; I felt so ashamed, so stupid, so ignorant and immature. I looked back into his rear-view mirror and saw that the stranger was smoldering with anger and disdain. He was probably cursing me out; I saw his mouth angrily spit several words that I was content not to hear.&lt;br/&gt;    This red light was eternal. I sat under his bewildered and furious stare for what felt like three millennia, trying as hard as I could to keep from meeting his stare and all the while making it worse by ignoring him. Finally, green triumphed over red and we awkwardly lurched forward. He raced off ahead of me and I breathed for the first time in years. &lt;br/&gt;    I’m such an idiot. Man... I felt, and still feel, beyond stupid and inconsiderate. How could I have mistaken him? How could I have messed like that with a complete stranger? He must hate me... and, honestly, at the moment I hoped he wouldn’t call the police on this crazy-haired short kid in a little red pick-up truck. &lt;br/&gt;    Truth is, he’ll forget me in a matter of days. I’ll forget too, but I make this record as something to laugh about in the future. *Sigh* Why do we do things like this?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from Walmart</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/joshuaeastman/Desktop/online/Online/Blog/Entries/2015/12/2_Lessons_from_Walmart.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2da639fb-c513-4972-a9ac-ce682c311ff3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 2 Dec 2015 20:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>Walking through Walmart troubles me.&lt;br/&gt;   Food--perfectly good and unopened containers of every sort of delicacy imaginable--is stockpiled over-abundantly, wasting away on the innumerable shiny white shelves. &lt;br/&gt;     People in this town go hungry. &lt;br/&gt;  Rack upon rack upon rack of shirts and jeans and underwear, clothes sitting, sitting, unused and unwanted.&lt;br/&gt;   So many people in my city, in my state, in my country, and in this world are without any clothes at all. &lt;br/&gt;     Both the food and the clothes sit, untouched and serving no purpose. That is, until a man or women with ample green in their wallet--albeit often hard-earned--comes along and buys them away. &lt;br/&gt;    The sight of the extreme opulence and waste makes me cringe... and yet I come home and find a dozen shirts I don’t wear hanging in my closet, a dozen pairs of socks wasting away in the back of my drawer, a dozen pairs of shorts and jeans sitting unused in my dresser, and a pantry and two fridges full of more food than my family could eat in two months, while I, like the complaining teenager I am, complain that we have nothing to eat. &lt;br/&gt;    Lord, have mercy on me; I am such a hypocrite. How can I accuse others of selfishness, greed, and cold disregard for the needs of others when I too commit the same acts of waste and inhospitality? Who am I to convict? Lord, have mercy on me; give me the courage to give fearlessly, the Spirit to love without regard to my own welfare. &lt;br/&gt;	Yes, the cold and indifferent luxury of Walmart troubles me, but there is something deeper, revealed in interacting with others in Walmart, which unsettles my soul even further.&lt;br/&gt;      Today I walked through the brightly lit, cheerily colored aisles of Walmart, looking for a replacement ink cartridge for my pen. I ran my hands along the shelves--smooth, cold metal--and breathed in the subtle aromas of of cleaning fluid, crowds, and rotisserie chicken. Sounds of distant babies crying, shopping-cart wheels squealing, and jumbled conversations tossed and turned in the air around me, creating an indistinct murmur that laid heavily over the whole store, and I, alone as I was, was forced to take all these things in, not distracted by a conversation with a friend or a parent as I usually am during Walmart visits. Also, and again because I had no company, I was obliged to take notice of the other people in the store, which is an absolutely terrifying prospect. I know that anyone who has passed a another living, breathing human being in the aisles of Walmart knows exactly the kind of palpable, anxious fear that wrenches your chest that I speak of.&lt;br/&gt;	I had two choices each time I passed someone; well, three, really, but the third is utterly preposterous. &lt;br/&gt;    The first and most ubiquitous instinct in an encounter with a foreign, unknown human being in Walmart is to hide your hands (usually in your pockets), hunch your shoulders, and stare at an unspecified point down and in the opposite direction of the body in question. Your step quickens and your face either becomes placid and emotionless or creased with unspoken anxiety and hurry while you shuffle awkwardly past. &lt;br/&gt;    The second choice, which was the one I weakly attempted to employ, is to actually look at the man or woman or child, and, having seen their eyes, to smile. Crazy, yes, and far more difficult than it indeed should be. The good thing about acknowledging the person with only a look and a smile is that you are not obligating the person to acknowledge you back, and as most others prefer the more instinctive option number one, you are often not seen and the forced smile is not returned. This lack of returned semi-greeting is somewhat of a relief, because then you’re invited to think of yourself as kinder and more hospitable than the other person, and self-inflation is always a good feeling... right?&lt;br/&gt;	The third, insanely ludicrous option, which I was never courageous enough to practice, is to say, gently, “Hello” or “Howdy” or “Hi there.” Of course, since none of us ever do this to strangers, when we first find ourselves attempting this kind of overt greeting all our words seem quite a bit too loud or terse or high-pitched; we become immediately self-conscious and exposed. However, and to our great surprise, these greetings usually merit a similarly awkward “Hello,” eye contact, and smile from the passerby.&lt;br/&gt;	Why, oh why, then, is it so hard to greet people? Though I did indeed make an effort to look people in the eye and give a somewhat kindly and natural smile, I do not by any means exclude myself from this question. Why am I so insecure, so self-absorbed, so afraid to gaze upon someone’s face, read the story written there, and be myself exposed to the same scrutiny? Why can’t I say hello to people? What is so anxiety-inducing about greeting someone good-naturedly? All my life, nearly all of my experience has taught me that nearly all people are nearly the same in nearly every aspect, especially when it comes to social misgivings and social desires. And yet, I still struggle to be a kind voice in a sea of unforgiving points and whispers. Why is this? &lt;br/&gt;	Lord, forgive me for my insecurity, forgive me of my cowardice, forgive me of my pride and selfishness and worry; I give all these parts of myself to You as captives. Refine me, put me through the crucible, and make me Gold. Wash me with the redemptive blood of Jesus Christ and make me clean, make me courageous, make me kind and humble and gentle and joyful, a fountain of Your Spirit. Help me love, Lord, as You love. You alone are good; I praise You forever and ever. Amen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Few Questions</title>
      <link>file://localhost/Users/joshuaeastman/Desktop/online/Online/Blog/Entries/2015/12/1_A_Few_Questions.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f381d8ac-0139-477f-961e-92d458b1525f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 1 Dec 2015 10:21:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <description>What makes a novel great? What about words brings them alive? What is in a story that makes the rolling syllables touch a man’s very soul, rattling his bones and blowing the dust off old photographs locked in the corners of the mind? Why are some paragraphs endlessly long yet concise, while short ones sometimes ramble forever? Why do words, so arranged on a page, produce rhythm, even poetry? And why should poetry affect us any different than prose? Does a letter have any power apart from the words it forms? Does reading silently kill the spirit of some words? Why do so many people struggle to read out loud? Why do writers often not like what they’ve written? Why does the first letter of every sentence need to be capitalized? Why are stanzas not simply called paragraphs? Why does ink stick so well to paper, and black look best against white? Why do we prefer writing in pen and not in pencil? &lt;br/&gt; Why must all things be analyzed?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
